Yeah,
yeah,
yeah
Don't ask me where to go Was
four seated tonight Tonight But when you do
But
my stacks many have died and many more
Okay,
I think some of the hospital
Yeah,
I can't help but smile with sunshine Aaron said to meet him at the sun Piles.
Maybe the time, I think
Damn all Surana stirring up tensions.
I'm keeping my eyes open.
Mhm
goes out of Won't cost you a sharp Just a look.
Don't pass up.
He's good.
Yeah.
Okay.
No.
Yeah.
He's trying
of all cities on within, in victory.
Okay,
there's what?
Yes.
Come take a look.
Give you a good price.
My bed charges.
Where's
mhm?
Move your wealth.
Okay.
It's so awesome.
Rama's building.
I may not have all the answers, but there is a book of bylaws here which can tell you more about the lodge.
Mm.
Suddenly you're a lot nicer.
I saw you talking to tell Lana she's tough.
You'd be lucky to keep up with her machine rider or no.
Wonderful.
Mhm.
Go on and give us cease those trophies.
You're seeing better.
I thought I told you I'm here to present trophies to the sun Hawk of the Lodge three saw tooths to ravage er's and a stalker for good measure.
I suppose Toe Lana helped you with this.
I brought these down myself.
Will you accept them?
Fine.
Yes, I accept them.
But tell tell Lana she should stop playing with sludge If she wants to get red, Mark
the culture of the South that could destroy a village and disappear into the hills.
I consider
Just
be
e gave him my trophies.
Asi said you should be spending more time finding Red Ma than helping me.
That bun head isn't wrong, but there isn't time to find.
Read more right now you're gonna help with something else.
Oh, and what might that be?
Meet me outside
a little sweat and hard work.
Never heard it
comes around what I'm gonna get.
I see
mhm from
way since it helped
for some Dio
Uh huh
Every time, Right.
Ethnicity
Gonna take a look Eyes
You want to help?
Here's someone who needs it.
Go ahead.
Al Saadi, I live in Lone Light northeast of here.
I barely escaped because glint hawks attack anyone who ventures out.
We have so few shots.
Will you help We have nowhere else to turn.
Sometimes members receiving honorarium for the hunt.
A C should have accepted this one, but he refused.
The price was too low.
How generous.
In the past, I would have gone with Talk us to handle this.
What say you and I take it on?
I'll meet you alone.
Life?
What about Red?
Ma?
Are you in or not?
All right.
I'll meet you there a soon as I can
about these.
I'll make sure all Saudi makes it back to loan light.
Meet you there.
It's just northeast of here.
Able bodied adventurers.
Preferably with no friends or family.
I'm not choosing.
Oh, they're Outlander names.
Ville gun.
Did you come to the city looking for work?
Good shards.
Enough to buy garb, more becoming okay, Stop there If you want me to hear you out, I only meant Ah, well molded woman such as you.
Uh huh.
Are you some kind of merchant?
You don't seem to have any wears more of an opportunist girl nor a girl, Huntress.
We live in a world of opportunities.
Risky opportunities.
But why should risk stand in the way of a lucrative prospect for the likes of me.
All right?
I'm more of a gambler.
I heard an interesting rumor about a Benue camp.
They say the Benue bear live alongside machines.
Peaceful is you, like, keep them, use them, sing to him.
If it's true, if we learned how they do it, think how valuable that would be.
Toe all the tribes when you say valuable, You mean they pay you for it?
Yeah.
The last bunch just wanted to know about the reward.
You're a smart one.
I hired men to investigate.
Just investigate.
That's all those ba Newkirk.
Canny, too canny.
I paid up front.
Well, half up front, I've had no word back.
So now you're hiring someone to find the last menu hired?
Mhm.
You're a sunk cost.
What can you tell me about the bannock with the Baluch women snow, which is all cold eyes cold.
Mhm.
They choose to live up there in bonheur in the ice, trying to have a conversation.
It's like chipping them out of the stuff.
They prefer machines for company.
That's why I'm putting my shards on this rumor.
Then they might not want outsiders to know about this place.
Uh huh.
their mystic act.
No care for possessions for luxuries, Pile of slag.
Those people bargain harder than the winter frost.
If I did look into your rumor, you won't need to climb up the shoulders of the world for it.
It's on the edge of the nuke land beneath the anvil of the moon.
And you look like you know your way around the savage east.
The east.
If it's true, they walk among machines without fear.
In this camp.
Well, you can't miss that, can you?
Payment on return.
You read.
Didn't wanna startle you?
No.
Yes.
I heard of the tragedy that befell your tribe.
The sun hung low that day as we traveled back.
So
this is the temple of the sun.
Priests where we offer are daily prayers for balance.
I'm afraid only carjack and participate.
But you are welcome to observe.
Don't worry, I'm used to it.
What are these prayers to recognize?
The sun is to recognize we live in renewal by its rise and fall.
We determine what to take up and what to set aside.
Offered to it's pure heat.
The skin peels and old time is burned away.
We treasure the blisters.
That sounds painful.
Well, there is no glory without sacrifice.
The temple looks out on the tower across the valley.
Why?
It is said that the spire's shadow lay across this mesa when our ancestors came to the valley searching for a home.
Thus, son inspire joy showing the Kharja where to build the dawn of Meridian.
Always illuminating, you read.
There is a matter not officially sanctioned.
That someone off your boldness.
You don't have to square married.
Let's hear it.
Uh, one of our brethren, my friend Norman, has stepped from the sun's light in protest.
I've supported his efforts as much as I can, But
would you speak with him in the sun?
Drink?
I'll see what I can do.
May you always go in light, my friend
Ha!
King of Odds Decree brought the Hunter's lodge in line here.
They had to admit another woman into the weeks.
It was
This is the spices
don't.
So
yeah, people keep spreading.
Thank you.
Was really in charge of Meridian, huh?
The OSCE, Iran.
That's who.
Whispering your son?
Kings
captain of the van murdered?
Yeah,
Military that she was destroyed.
Good.
Serious.
What's your
shadow?
Cardiac ambushed Captain IRSA
did they?
Mhm.
Thank you.
It's just that
No,
it's about time.
This is a toilet.
Listen
too much.
You're Nora.
I'm the mournful Newman.
My apologies that we need like this.
Like this in grief.
You hold yours close like a talisman.
Wait.
Forgive me.
You didn't come for reparations.
Someone you lost to the sun ring.
No, I know about the red raids, but the card you owe me Nothing.
I see.
Well, I could use the help of a strong wheeled Outlander.
Then I would owe you very much indeed.
I didn't think your priesthood would ask outsiders for help.
If only the sun would sat on our pride until this is done.
I am no son.
Priest toe wear a red robe was an aspiration.
I aspired.
Now our herds make us blind.
We whisper reconciliation, But forget how the old kings priests sang the words and bless the killing.
You're disappointed with the sun priests, but you still wanted to be one.
I spent my whole life looking up to the temple, my brother's voice echoing in his arches.
Even he couldn't turn me away And how he tried in the end
he said.
When we were loved, our robes were died in cinnabar.
Now they're stained in blood.
How so?
Our robes handed down to us.
Most of the old priests fled rather than be seen in the glare of a new son.
And so we left aware their sins for me.
At least they hang heavy.
Where is your brother now?
He waits for me on the trail of the sun.
I hope
he spoke out against the sacrifices
for a priest to question the Sun Kings.
Will, His punishment was worst of all.
You lost someone you loved to.
I'm sorry.
No, not lost.
When I took on these robes,
I found his memory.
Why did the priests go along with all that bloodshed?
Sometimes we Karger are more concerned with what is tradition than what is right.
Uh huh.
Maybe the Kharja and Nora aren't so different.
These people seek toe honor their loved, their lost with their own voices, not mouthing Kharja rituals to card a stone.
But there are obstacles.
While Meridian hold his breath for any disturbance, these robes only tie my hands.
What kind of obstacles?
The first program is a Nocera who seeks to visit the shrine of kings on the road to the city.
He wastes her, now forbidden to enter by an old son priest who suffer.
No, he, Ethan,
this you Taro lost her companion on the edge of Jule at a pool with snap malls.
Gather Shrine was built, their toe walled off the machines, and it's effectiveness leaves much to be desired.
And the men Ouk would paint a mark on the sun's climb called to the machine spirits.
I understand
they need no beckoning Clint Hawks perched there,
drawn to the spires, shining so clear the machines out of two shrines and move a priest out of the other.
All I can ask for is your charity and that their stories are heard.
Newman rituals and prayers can't bring back those who are lost.
No, but it can help those who grieve to find themselves.
It could lend them strength and hope, like a new sunrise.
I'll do what I can to help those in mourning toe honor their memories is to honor us all.
You're not like the others.
You wear machine parts, but you hunted them yourself.
How can you tell?
Ah Hunter knows a hunter.
My people run with the great metal herds among the northern glaciers.
But the glint hawks its sons climb are too strong for me.
So I cannot fulfill my vow to paint the story of my people there.
How the madness of the machines spread to the Kharja and they sent their soldiers feet frost black and to bring his here in chains.
Our Sharman's who sing the machine songs Many were taken to their deaths.
Their songs go unfinished and bonheur
help me honor them.
Help me paint their story I ask you this hunter to hunter
You look like you've traveled far Outlander from the Great Plains but not alone.
Never alone.
This was the city of cages to harvest ago
Wooden bars leave marks.
I kept those marks.
I can still feel the bars They took you as a slave But you escaped during the liberation.
My friend and I, they put us to work in the chorus together we've grown alike So we fled together.
But in the smoke the trees we ran right into the machines I kept running.
I thought she was just behind me.
She is still wherever I go just behind me.
That's why I came back to finally free us from that moment.
But I need your help to do it.
I've been asking the nobles of the Sun Court to hear on my cause.
Just the grace of their ears.
You want me to shake them down too?
Don't tempt me.
I'm still a priest.
I need to get going.
May the sun shine upon you.
I'll never leave Meridian, if you alone makes life worthwhile.
Always stay bright.
Always stay alert.
That's what I say
to get smashed.
Meridian is the center of the world.
Everyone comes here eventually.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah!
No moving and alert.
God damn it!
Yes,
Jim, That's really
stable.
We still
Ah, you're everything.
I'm not strong.
Brave active.
Come talk a spell.
All right.
What did you want to discuss?
You're an Outlander, which is good, but a Nora which might be bad.
Do you fear the ruins of the old ones?
Like many in your tribe?
No.
Although some could be dangerous.
Then you may have come across what I seek in your travels.
Have you found strange vessels emblazoned with symbols of the old ones?
They consist of?
Ah, hollow cylinder with a crescent handle.
A fixed at both ends.
If you bring me these vessels in sets of four, I will gladly trade what I have for them.
So you are interested in the old ones?
More than interested.
I study every ancient artifact I could get my hands on.
But years of study have made me too comfortable at my desk.
I can't even bear the sun.
If the truth be known.
I don't know how I'll manage to take a partner.
My family presses me for an air.
Don't look at me.
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm not looking.
In fact, my father already has someone he wants me to wed.
She doesn't interest me.
I wish I had a brother to carry this burden.
I would rather be left to my precious little vessels.
What sort of ritual?
Where these vessels made for I'm convinced they were used in conjunction with each other in sets.
Some people believe they were used for tea ceremonies.
Others think they held sacred essences and oils for worship.
But I believe they were used for the solemn custom of shaving one's beard.
One for water, one for lotion and so on each fluid in its special vessel majestically applied to the face at each stage of the right.
It must have been breathtaking.
But which vessel was used for which I have to know.
I have to continue my research.
Are you sure people didn't just drink out of them?
Drink out of such finally crafted earthenware?
Don't be ridiculous.
I will leave you to the hunt.
Be sure to delve into the ruins.
I like Meridian fines, but for further country.
Or at least I did before.
The machine's got so bad.
Yeah,
okay.
Yeah.
Services.
No.
Right.
Okay.
Wow!
How about this ceasefire?
The Sundram prospers, son.
Fall will want a piece of it eventually.
Who's gonna leave the bank card now?
Erin the boys.
A drunken Rexes
son.
Kennecott hasn't got the stones to put an end of those trading since
place in the order.
Okay.
Good day.
No shadows under the noonday sun.
Words to everybody.
No shadows under the noonday sun Words delivered.
Greetings a lie.
I am known as blameless.
Murad, please come with me.
You're needed for an important consultation.
What do you mean?
Where's Errand?
He's inside.
Attending the Sun King where we should be without further delay.
Follow me, please.
The Sun King is eager to meet you.
The machine Tamil with curious eye for detail.
It's all very intriguing.
I'm not here to intrigue you.
Too late.
All of these people are here to see the sun came.
Yes, on beach has come to ask a favor.
Off unpleasant.
But that's politics.
First the ass Iran gets special treatment.
And now outlanders from a savage least possible interest.
Could the sun came having her
passed by some outlined a woman un except I've been here for two hours.
Miss Nora, go to the front of the line.
Ignore them.
Nobles are like Children who wine when they don't get a second helping of dessert.
What's the sun came like The most important thing is what he isn't like his father.
I think you'll find him to be a reasonable man.
A lawyer of the Nora, She who sees the unseen welcome.
It would seem you have done me a great service
errand.
Tell her what you found.
I checked Ercis tomb.
You were right away.
The body is missing.
Scar below her right knee.
I gave it to her So when we were kids fighting over a toy sword.
The body is not er says that we must assume she is still alive and I will not abandon her.
We only know she was taken.
Not who took her.
I can help with that.
Ursa has an enemy among the Osoro.
Ah, Warlord named Darva.
Impossible.
Every clan in the claim has been hunting for him since the liberation.
He has to be dead by now.
No other Ostrom had the motive and ingenuity to lure are so into this trap.
I expect to find him lurking somewhere near the border.
I've already sent an agent to investigate.
He'll be waiting for word from us at the market place in pitch Cliff.
I can't move troops to the border without provoking the Osirak.
But I could send a few Van Guardsmen
and perhaps an exceptionally gifted Nora as well.
Errant Murad, let me discuss it with her privately.
I hate to impose further after all you've done, but this is a matter of great importance to me.
It sounds like Carson means a lot to you.
Without her a serum vanguard, I would not have been able to liberate Meridian and end my father's brutal reign.
Since then, it has been difficult to maintain peace between our tribes,
but also has a way of making her people see reason.
So you see, I need her back at my side.
And quickly.
Why would Derval go to so much trouble to kidnap IRSA?
He felt she betrayed him.
She fought by his side until she realized he planned to raise Meridian and butcher its people.
And she came to me
together.
We stopped him and liberated the city from my father.
He truly thought of himself as a sun God.
His mind was broken.
They believe that blood sacrifice would solve well, everything.
So he raided the other tribes for victims, especially the Asaro.
Derval fought back.
He crafted powerful weapons and rallied his people.
My father responded with the ultimate cruelty.
He captured durables, wife and daughter
and sacrifice them in the sun ring.
Derval has spent every moment since trying to get revenge.
Your politics seem very complicated, Theus.
Our, um our friends, but enemies too.
I couldn't have liberated Meridian without the help of Ursa and her.
A serum Free borders.
Many of them have settled here
But the elderman of the Ostrom clans and the claim have become jealous of their success.
So have many cards and nobles.
It's a volatile situation, especially given the fact that my father raided the OSCE Iran for years.
Ursa helps keep the peace
promising a future based on mutual game.
But some, like Derval, will never let go of their venom.
I'd like to ask you something about the Sunda Minutes politics, by all means.
What can you tell me about the Shadow?
Kharja?
What do they have to do with Ursa?
They are remnants of my father's regime holding out at the fortress of Sun Fall to the west
like him, they care only for domination
and sick to draw upon the power of the sun by spilling blood in its name.
Since Ursa helped me take this city from them, they were perfect scapegoats.
Derval knew this, of course, been planted Well, I need to get going.
I know.
Well,
they say King should never beg.
But please help me find our son.
Who says that?
Murad, for one,
don't hesitate to ask him or errand if you have further questions.
It's not why I imagine boy but it's decent work keeping the city safe.
Hey Long, How can I be of service?
Why did they call you blameless Murad?
Well, it depends on who you mean by that.
And what they might wish to blame me for.
Talking to you is tiring.
So they say.
What is it you do exactly whatever is needed?
Of course.
Are you always so evasive?
It depends.
You were right about a VOD.
He seems genuine.
He is the Sun king.
I serve him the best I can.
Uh huh.
Did you serve?
The last one is best.
You could too.
Well, I served him to his enemies.
It was the best I could do for the Sunday Um what did you do?
Nothing I could be blamed for.
What will I find at the border on outpost, Full of a serum most of whom want nothing to do with Derval.
Still, he inspires great loyalty in those who fought with him against the last son came.
He will not be caught alone.
And don't forget he is a master craftsman.
Nothing delights him more than his dangerous toys.
What makes you so sure Devil did this to IRSA?
I don't care for sure or certain I prefer likely.
Or probably
how Maney also remark.
Clever Now for this.
Roofs capable of building the weapon you describe who hate Ursa so
more than one.
Not likely Darvon.
Quite a problem.
Even if people think he's dead, that is surely another reason to be suspicious of certain words.
It's time for me to leave.
It would appear so
Yeah, So I thought Ursa was dead and I thought Derval was dead.
Dad doesn't seem to mean what it used to.
All I know is that it's time to find my sister and get some Tayback.
I hope my rods guy grabs us the lead.
Did Ursa ever tell you anything about Devil?
We were both under his command for a while.
Sort of helped him recruiting army to take out the mad some king.
But then he got really creepy with Ursa.
Needless to say, she wasn't interested that he wouldn't let it go.
Not to mention the fact that we realized he wanted to murder every Kharja.
Not just the bad ones.
Long story short, he's a grazer licking done bag.
A VOD seems committed to finding your sister.
Yeah, Those two got along and some people say they shacked up, but I don't buy it.
Seems a little skinny for her.
Okay, Some bad images, air forming in my head.
Let's just focus on finding her and kicking dirt balls.
Ass.
Don't stand me up in pitch cliff.
Okay?
Person needs us.
Mhm.
Help burning a son again.
I'm doing
okay.
Refused?
Yeah.
I couldn't imagine living anywhere else.
Suit she just
Bye.
Laws of the Hunters Lodge.
Section one Preamble 1.1.
The hunt is the Nobelist pursuit in the Sunday um, save those of the Sun King and his son priests.
The hunt is strength.
The hunt is on er the hunt protects the hunt.
Preserves 1.2.
What is the hunt of competition?
What is competition with that Rank Honor and Victor 1.3.
The large lens law and lower to the hunt.
So all will know who has prevailed 1.4.
Thus the lodge is not just its members and not just its house in Meridian.
It is the spirit of the hunt.
A code to be honored, an ideal to be lived 1.5 on Lee.
Those of the noble ist blood can embody the noble ist ideals.
As such Onley card emails of pure blood may honor the lodge and trend.
It's house 1.6 By order of his radiance of odd 14th Sun, King of the Kharja file All five of section one is hereby rescinded.
Section two Membership 2.1 No hunter shall gain admittance to the lodge without three half sons One with honor at any hunting ground See section five below 2.2 There are two classes of Member Hawk being senior thrush being junior 2.3 The rank of thrush can only begin through the sponsorship of a hawk Each hawk may sponsor only one thrush 2.4 There can be only seven hawks.
Ah thrush can only become a hawk through the death of his sponsor 2.5 The hawk who hunts the greatest pray shall become son Hawk and lead the lodge 2.6 In the event, the quality of prey is in dispute.
The hawk who hunted first shall remain first as son Hawk 2.7 Onley card emails of pure blood may become Thrush Hawk or son Hawk 2.8 by order of his radiance of odd 14th Sun, King of the Kharja, by lost seven of section two is hereby rescinded.
Section three Proof of the hunt 3.13 Greatest hunts often bear no witness.
Therefore, a trophy must be kept 3.2.
A trophy may be submitted to the Sun Hawk is proof of a victorious hunt 3.3 a trophy must be intact undamaged and from a recent hunt 3.4, the Son Hawk shall have final authority in any dispute Over a trophies worth 3.5 Onley card emails of pure blood may submit a trophy to the Sun Hawk 3.6 by order of his radiance of odd 14th sun, King of the Kharja by all five of section three is hereby rescinded Section four to protect and preserve 4.1.
Ah, hunt for its own sake is noble.
Ah, hunt in the service of others is blessed by the sun 4.2 when called upon, hawks and thrushes must undertake any reasonable hunt asked of them if it serves to protect the citizens of the Sunday um 4.3 son Hawk has sole authority to negotiate any fees or bounties associated with any hunt undertaken by members of the lodge on behalf of the Sunday um 4.4.
Any profit from any hunt undertaken by members of the lodge on behalf of the Sunday um shall be shared by all seven hawks administered by the Sun Hawk 4.5 on Lee Card emails of pure blood may undertake a hunt in the name of the lodge, Be it for the protection of the Sunday um or any other reason?
4.6.
By order of his radiance of odd 14th sun King of the Kharja five, all five of section for is hereby rescinded Section five hunting grounds 5.1 For the purpose of training and recruiting the best and greatest hunters, the lodge shall provide and maintain hunting grounds 5.2 each.
Hunting ground shall test a different range of skills through three trials crafted by its keeper in consultation with the Sun Hawk 5.3, there shall be three rewards for each trial in ascending order of performance.
Half son full sun blazing sun.
5.4 hunters who proved themselves by winning the requisite number of sons may be entitled to special gear of the lodge at the discretion of the Sun Hawk 5.5, the lodge shall provide funds for the construction and maintenance of all trials and facilities at hunting grounds.
5.6 The lodge shall receive all profits associated with the sale of parts, ammunition and equipment from all hunting grounds.
5.7 Any profits received from hunting ground shall be shared by all seven hawks administered by the Sun Hawk.
5.8 keepers shall be chosen exclusively by the Sun Hawk and serve for a term of seven years.
5.9 Onley card emails of pure blood may be appointed keeper 5.10 By order of his radiance of odd 14th sun, King of the Kharja, by longing of Section five is hereby rescinded.
The founding of Meridian wear Kharja in us is the blood of those led by Armand from persecution and pursuit.
So long ago, out of the far savages we came guardians of the treasure greater than land or metal.
The leaves of the old ones, Armand found, believes in the ruin picked out by a beam of sunlight and he recognized it once.
Their importance within was such the first teachings of how to observe the sun, to recognize its guidance and to understand the place of man.
From out of the leaves came the first cliffs, the first writing so our knowledge could last longer than voices.
But when our forefathers offered to share this gift, they were driven out by those they had once called Tribe spoke thes ones feared to have the light of knowledge brought to bear on their ignorance or were jealous of its power.
And so began a long wandering of our people, trusting only that the sun would guide them and deliver them from the barbarian tribes.
Path was hard and marked by the stones of families who fell along the wayside.
Even our man's own persecution was unceasing from those without purpose on Lee the desire to debase and destroy.
But the faith of the cargo was rewarded with a distant vision, a tower like a solid ray of the sun holding on the horizon, flashing even as their enemies descended upon them.
Armand followed the flight of the glint hawks, leading his people through looming canyons and teaming jungles.
Again, they saw the tower so close now it seemed to reach the very sun itself, and they saw that the glint hawks perched upon it be held in the light of the sun.
The tower, the spire cast its long shadow upon a mesa across the verdant valley are Emma knew he had found a haven for the tribe, as this was a place shunned by those without his faith, who cowered from the magnificence of the spire or the shining feathers of the glint talks.
He named this place Meridian from a passage in the leaves, and the tribe settled in the protection of the Great Mesa.
They found the site was blessed in every respect.
Carving their cliff houses from the bounteous resource is and in time from the red rock of Mesa itself, crowning it with the first columns of the City of the Sun.
Truly, the son gave much to the descendants of our forefathers, granting meridian great harvests and prosperity and the bounds of the sun.
And for us faras, it's light touched in time.
Seeing Meridian shielded us from the dark arrows and plots of our foes.
Other foreigners brought trade and tribute.
Holy Meridian without spire and son, There would be no meridian.
But now and forever more.
It stands this monument to both.
And the glory of Arman and the Founders is reflected a new in each sun, King of the Radiant line and the noble houses of the Sun Court.
Yeah!
Mhm!
All right.
Thank you, Mr.